

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

> Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Mr. Ribeiro

NATIONALITY: Brazilian and Portuguese

SUMMARY

Desire to act professionally and add value to the Company in positions related as Supervisor, Coordinator, Consultant, Auditor, Finance and Business Analyst, Business Support and others, based on previous experiences in the areas of Consulting and Audit Process (Internal Controls) and Information Systems.

Currently ex-worker at PwC (PricewaterhouseCoopers) as Consultant and Auditor Process and IT. I am graduated in Business Administration and I have the course in Accounting stopped in the 4th period. I possess effective communication in English and Portuguese and I can understand Spanish in regular communication. Dual citizenship (Brazilian and Portuguese) which may encourage me to travel possible by the company and I do not need any work permit. I have international experience due to two exchanges, one for South Africa and one for Canada. Leadership experience in the Brazilian Air Force. Willingness to travel and change (including international). Experience in internal controls over 3 years.

EDUCATION

Qualified Bachelor level of Business (Undergraduate study)

EMPLOYMENT RECORD

Consultant and Audit of Process

- PricewaterhouseCoopers July 2010 to May 2013
- **PricewaterhouseCoopers** March 2007 to June 2010

Staff of the armed forces

Brazilian Air Force, Belo Horizonte (Brazil)
 First ClassSoldier - Specialization in Basic Mechanics of Aircraft



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Consultant and Audit of Process

PricewaterhouseCoopers - July 2010 to May 2013

Main Activities:

- Mapping risks, design, implementation and testing of internal control systems (ERP: SAP, TOTVS,Oracle) and business processes(costs, accounts payable and receivable).
- General Controls Audit of Information Technology, including the evaluation and testing of internal controls for information security, development and change programs and computerized operations.
- Participation in projects Consulting SAP Segregation of functions, including activities such as defining the risk matrix, redesign of access profiles and creating and implementing access governance.
- Participation in Consulting mapping and diagnosis of internal controls Araujo
 Drugstore.
- Participation in a Consulting mapping, assessment and redesign of controls at a Multinational Petronas (Petronas Lubricants Brazil).
- Main Clients: Petronas, ESAB, Usiminas, Vale (VLI: FCA, FNS, VOF), EMH, ESCO Soldering, Magnesita, Nemak, Novo Nordisk, SMC, Brembo, Curimbaba, Cedro, Seven Boys, Itambé, DAMP, SMSA and Araujo.
- Business or sector Audit

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS
n/a
PUBLICATIONS
n/a

LANGUAGES

English, Portuguese, Spanish